http://www.sabatinostore.com/pages/privacy-policy-1

Privacy Policy 2020
This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from sabatinostore.com and sabatinotruffles.com (the “Sites”).
PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECTWhen you visit the Sites, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Sites, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Sites, and information about how you interact with the Sites. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.We collect Device Information using the following technologies:- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, click here.- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Sites, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Sites.Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Sites, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Sites (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:- Communicate with you;- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Sites (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Sites, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATIONWe share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Sites -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here.Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.BEHAVIORAL ADVERTISINGAs described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page here.You can opt out of targeted advertising by clicking here.DO NOT TRACKPlease note that we do not alter our Sites' data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.YOUR RIGHTSIf you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Sites), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.DATA RETENTIONWhen you place an order through the Sites, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.CHANGESWe may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.CONTACT USFor more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at customer@sabatinostore.com or by mail using the details provided below:SABATINO NORTH AMERICA[Re: Privacy Compliance Officer]135 Front AvenueWest Haven, CT 06516customer@sabatinostore.com
FACEBOOKWe also use the pixel function of Facebook Custom Audiences to identify users who have landed on certain pages for the purposes of target group-orientated remarketing and advertising. The Facebook pixel stores a cookie, which means that information about your visit to our Mailchimp Site will be shared with Facebook. Also, as part of the "advanced matching" undertaken by Facebook, other personal information (such as telephone number, email address, Facebook ID) may be shared with Facebook in a protected (hashed) form. These cookies and the information collected are used to create target groups to help Facebook deliver advertising on our behalf to users who have previously visited our Mailchimp Site when they are on Facebook or a digital platform powered by Facebook Advertising, and to track advertising success. You can modify your Facebook Ad settings to restrict these advertisements. Navigate to Settings/Adverts in your Facebook account to adjust your preferences. Learn more about the different types of Facebook cookies here: https://www.facebook.com/policies/cookies/
Truffle Newsletter
Stay up to date on the latest truffle news and discounts.
Close (esc)
Popup
Use this popup to embed a mailing list sign up form. Alternatively use it as a simple call to action with a link to a product or a page.
Age verification
By clicking enter you are verifying that you are old enough to consume alcohol.
Your cart is currently empty.
Shop now
